Now, so, Hakata...
Here we are at the observation deck.
Amazing!
Refreshing!
This time we are going to exchange
What a way to cross the sea!
We are going to Busan!
This time
We will be taking that ferry, so...
Oh!
We're going on the Queen Beat.
You're going on the Queen Beat?
Oh!
Thank you for your hard work.
Seino
Ha-ha-ha-ha
It's hard.
A-ha-ha-ha
difficult
Difficult
So, here we are on the second day of Japan-Korea exchange, and to our surprise, a Korean student has come to take us around today.
Where are you taking us today?
There is a bridge over there where you can see the ocean, take pictures, and stand on the glass bottom,
You can see the ocean, take pictures, and feel like you are standing on the ocean.
Wow, it's fun! It's pretty good, you know.
How about you, Japanese students? I've been here for two days until today.
It was fun. I also had a chance to interact with Korean students.
I'm glad that we got to know each other better.
I'm looking forward to interacting with many people again today.
I'm looking forward to it.
What do you think, Ai-chan?
I haven't done much sightseeing in Pusan.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Are you okay? You don't like heights?
Yes, I'm sure.
I can do it.
Are you okay?
You're not scared?
Oh!
Today, to further strengthen the bonds between Japan and Korea.
I'd like to do something nutritional.
You want to do something nutritional?
I want to do something nutritional.
How do you say AO in Korean?
In Korean, it's Aja Fighting.
Fighting.
Okay, I'm going to say this in three, two, one, and we'll do it together.
Put your hands out in front of you.
Ready.
Aja Fighting
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I want to do it again.
You just said that.
Okay.
Aja Fighting.
Is it all glass?
Yeah, it's all glass down there.
This whole place is glass.
Maybe not.
It's like being on the ocean.
That's scary.
There's a lot of sea.
So many things.
Hey...
The ocean
I know what you mean.
It looks so beautiful.
Oh, man.
Oh, no!
I see what you mean.
Shoes?
You put them on over your shoes, like a cover.
That's funny.
Even if there's glass underneath, it won't hurt them.
I think the glass will make a very nice view.
Here you go.
Oh, wow.
That's amazing.
It's so beautiful.
It's beautiful.
So beautiful.
I'm so embarrassed to be here.
Can you see Japan?
Japan? Where's Japan?
Oh, my God!
Shall we go?
It's so beautiful! It's also...
But it's surprisingly accessible.
You're coming in fast.
But it looks like wakame seaweed.
Wakame seaweed?
Wakame seaweed.
Down here.
Is this it?
Oh, yes, yes, yes.Oh, it's true, it's true, it's true.
Like a big wakame seaweed.
Wakame, wakame?
Is that a wakame?
There's a big one under it.
There's a big one.
It might be a shark.
What?
Maybe it's a big shark.
A shark.
We're gonna lose this place.
I'm not waiting.
I won't give it to you.
I don't have it.
What? What?
Heart?
What? Is it broken?
You're right!
Hold on, hold on.
Come on!
Friendship!
This is bad.
Okay, let's lose.
What is this?
It won't kill you.
It's strong.
Is it really?
It's definitely heavy.
But maybe you should have taken a picture of it here.
Yeah, for sure.
You should take a picture, Ai.
Let's all take a picture together.
Sure, let's all bond together.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
I see... we're all connected here.
This is our daily bond.
Is this in the picture?
Let's go deepen it.
I'm coming, 321.
I'll go one more time.
I think I've got a little bug hair.
I'm sure.
We have a bond.
Yay!
Jump?
Go softly.
Just be gentle. Just give me a second.
Let's go softly.
I'm scared
Video.
Okay, let's go this way.
Ready? Ready?
Wow.
That's funny.
That was a bumpy ride.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
It's okay. We're connected by our bond.
Spread?
Wider?
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Scary.
You think I can see without climbing?
Laughing.
Can you see it?
Oh, my God, I can see it!
Really?
How far can you see?
I don't know.
It's kind of white.
Oh, over there.
You can see the white bumps.
A white knob?
I don't see them at all.
Oh, no!
I see a boat!
Look!
I can see it!
I see ships!
So many boats!
There are people on the island!
There are people on the island.
Here, here, here.
Try not to move it and you'll see.
There are people on this tiny little island.
It's real.
Oh, my God, it's real.
That's amazing.
I can see it on the Marito River.
How are we gonna get there?
By boat?
Did they go by boat?
You can't swim there.
Of course not.
That way! Straight ahead.
That's the boat.
Can you see it clearly? The ship?
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
We're moving forward to the right.
Advancing.
Watch out for the rocks.
Be careful moving forward.
Be careful.
Oh, my God, there's so many of them. They're really floating.
There's a lot of them, right? Something's doing its best to avoid them.
I want to see the ship. It's going straight.
I can see the ship.
I'm doing my best to steer with one hand.
That's the one you're thinking of, the one at the back.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, it's a small boat.
It's a small boat. One man on board.
One person on board. What did you see?
Maybe he was up there doing something like this.
I didn't see that.
I was driving as fast as I could.
There's a lot of money up there.
It's like...
Fighting!
Hey, guys, I know a great spot.
Let's go.
I think we should take a picture together.
Bye spot?
Yeah, there's a spot where they say it's okay to stand.
I see.
I think it's right here.
I think it's great up here, just the two of us.
Here?
Here.
What? Just a little bit.
This is a great spot to get laid.
Are you sure?
Can you stand up?
This is about right.
No, no, no. I think the top one's probably better.
Best position.
Standing on one leg?
Bight rear.
How's the bite?
That's a great angle, Bittoria.
Oh, that's good.
Happy life.
Three, two, one.
How'd it go? We walked on that glass, didn't we?
We walked on top of that glass, weren't we scared shitless?
Yeah, but we were lying down. We were sitting down.
We took some wow pictures.
And we had a lot of bonding time with everyone.
It was a lot of fun.
I feel safer when I can see the ocean, Japan.
Japan?
I don't know, but the sea in Korea is really impressive, isn't it?
Yeah, I know.
Eiffel Tower? The University of Tokyo?
It's close by.
It's like we've gone to France.
Across the ocean.
It's amazing, back there and in the sky.
Poussin view.
Poussin and...
It's nice, this kind of festival.
Stylish.
It's great.
Where are you going next?
I don't know.
Oh, yes, they're taking a bus right now.
Let's head there and see where we're going.
Let's go.
Asia Asia Fighting.
Where are we?
Well, in Japanese, it's called Ganchun Village.
The buildings are quite colorful.
And there are many murals painted on the walls.
There are photo spots like this.
It's a great spot for couples on a date.
Cute! So colorful!
What's that behind?
Yes, if you look at the back.
Fish?
Yes, sir.
What's your famous inside story?
It's pretty famous on Instagram and stuff.
When you go on Instagram, there's a place where there's the hall of the prince of the stars.
You sit next to it and take a picture from the back.
You can see the whole cultural district from there.
It's designed in such a way that you can see many buildings at once.
So you can take a picture there.
Wow!
Let's take pictures there, for sure!
I'll take pictures!
Is there anything you would like to be photographed like?
Long legs and small face.
Realistic.
Shall we do it then?
Yes, I'll do it.
Paul, please.
Oh, I'm out.
Hannah, two, three, nay!
Aja! Aja! Fighting!Aja! Aja! Fighting!
It's so high.
Cute.
It's true.
It's amazing.
I went to your house.
Wow!
That's great.
He's so cute.
It's amazing. Why is it so colorful?
Amazing.
It's so cute.
There are so many colors.
What are you looking at?
Pink! There's so much pink!
There's yellow!
Isn't there a lot of blue?
Maybe blue is the most common.
There's yellow too!
Lots of light pink!
Yes! Pretty!
This is beautiful!
Nice to meet you!
Oh, my gosh! It's so cute!
It's so cute!
It's so colorful!
So colorful!
Amazing!
A little more colorful!
Yeah!
Wow!
I can see your face.
You're flying.
You're fly.
Do you have toys in your color?
Oh, yes, I do!
Lots of blue.
You don't usually see purple.
I'm so happy.
Oh, wow!
Osmi
Osumi Osumi
Oh, wow!
Wow, wow, wow!
Beautiful.
Wow!
So colorful!
Amazing!
The peaks are beautiful.
Mayuka, you're amazing!
Amazing.
I'm with Mayuka
Wow, so beautiful!
So colorful!
I saw it on the way here.
What color do you like?
I, uh, I don't know what color I like.
Smoo would have to be blue, blue.
It's so famous.
I like blue for a burn.
I like blue for the body.
Blue body.
It's hard to choose.
What color do you like?
I like green
I like green.
Oh, it's pretty.
Green and purple is cute.
Like smash.
What color do you like?
I like Alyce.
Brick? Pink?
Pink.
It's so pretty.
That's so Parisian.
Oh, my God.
I thought it was over here.
That's not the place.
It's fantastic.
Yeah, it's definitely a toy.
It sure looks like Legos.
It's definitely not Japanese.
It's like Lego.
That's a lot of space.
I heard there are people who live here.
I wonder...
It's like living in a Ghibli world!
I lived here.
That's for sure!
I'm filming.
Oh, it's filming.
Please subscribe to our channel!
How was it, Japanese students?
Normally, you can't communicate directly with Korean people.
So even though there's a language barrier.
I was happy to be able to communicate with them through movement and so on.I was happy if I could communicate by movement and so on.
I was happy to learn about various cultures.
When I came to Korea for the first time
I didn't know if I would be able to get along at first.
but everyone around me was very kind to me.
I was able to make friends with Korean people and Batten people.
I'm glad I did.
I had a lot of fun talking with the people in Korea and the people at the restaurant.
I had a lot of fun talking with Korean people and the people at the restaurant,
I was able to go sightseeing in many places.
I was able to experience things that I can't experience in Japan with many people, so I have good memories.
I still have a lot more to do and a lot more food to eat.
I hope to be able to have the same experience again with the people from Batten and the people from Korea.
It was a great experience for me because I was able to go to places that I don't go to when I travel to Korea.
I am glad that everyone had a good time together.
I was happy to be able to experience various aspects of Korean culture during my two days in Korea, and it was a lot of fun.
Well then, please keep it steady for the rest of the day in Korea. How was it?
I felt the brightness of youth, a little bit like a stab in the heart.
It was a lot of fun!
Thank you very much.
The Japanese students were young and excited.
I was energized in many ways.
I'm glad it was so much fun!
Mostly.
Very popular.
I'm glad they got excited and had fun playing with high school students!
So thank you again for two days!
I'll be back.
Thank you for your hard work
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Which one?
The pink one.
Oh, it's pink.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
There you go. I thought it was this way.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, wait a minute.
We didn't understand each other.
Oh, my God, I have no idea.
Thank you.
Oh, my God, you idiot.
Welcome home.
Yum! Yum!
Come on!